we need a rest of the app I know they
exist
the crates your meal plan but do you
believe that and it when I talked about
the very beginning but really food is
very important we can talk about it too
much so a food app that allows you to
find recipes for things that meet your
needs so if you're on a specific diet
you have multiple people even together
that are all on specific diets help you
plant them then you tell you where it's
available if you got all that from
before we can buy the food tells you how
to prepare it crush everything that
makes life easier but mainly if you've
ever been on a restricted diet finding
recipes that work especially if you're
also feeding other people have different
restrictions you have allergies so a
better food and new creation tool is
number 93